Finding Aid for the Jason Brown Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- “Reinvention” Mail Art Project
  - Jeremy Jones (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Kate Gilbert (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Louisiana, USA (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cuan Miles (Front & Back) - South Africa (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cristina Rios Leme ‘Reinvencao’ - Brazil (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Richard Canard (Front & Back) - Illinois, USA (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Bradford Brooks - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - ARK ‘Stamps’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ryosuke Cohen (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Japan (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Scotland (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Duncan Ragsdale (Envelope-Front & -Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - John Guider ‘The Last Polaroid’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CASCADIA ARTPOST (Envelope-Front & -Back, Insert-Front & -Back) - Washington, USA (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Scotland (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Charmaine R Thionville, Louisiana, USA (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sheri Rice (Front & Back) - California, USA (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Chuck Beard (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Michael Orr & Diane Keys (Envelope-Front & -Back, Insert-Front & -Back) - Georgia, USA (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Maria Gammon, Texas, USA (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Sinead Bligh ‘Wha’ you take me a fool roun’ here’ (Inserts & Letter) - England (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - FIELD STUDY ? David Dellafiora (Envelope-Front, ‘Reinvention’-Front & -Back, Various Inserts) - Australia (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Scotland (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - John Yandall - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Daniel Stanley Aponte (Sub-Real Alchemy) (Front & Back) - Indiana, USA (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Michael Goetz - Illinois, USA (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lori Odom ‘General Jasper’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rebecca Resinski (Front & Back) - Arizona, USA (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Leslie Martensen, California, USA (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - John Guider ‘Portrait of Jason Brown for The Nashville Arts Magazine’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Lindsey Bailey & Sarah Johnson (Envelope-Front & -Back) - Lindsey Bailey (Front & Back) - Sarah Johnson (Front & Back) - Singapore (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Rosanna Veronesi (Front & Back) - Italy (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lori Odom ‘Play Dog & his bitches’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Consuelo Debiagi (Front & Back) - Brazil (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Anne Bossenbroek (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Willemien Visser (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Richard Canard (Front & Back) - Illinois, USA (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Douglas Galloway ‘Close Order Lattice’ - Washington, USA (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Morocco (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Back) - FRONT DETACHED DURING TRANSIT THROUGH POSTAL SYSTEM - California, USA (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Victor Femenias (Insert-Front & -Back) - Chile (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - BA Graphic Design Students at Chelsea College of Art & Design - London, England (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Platetone Open Studio Workshop PARTS 1-3 - Nashville, Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - John Butler - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Megan Kelley (Front & Back, Full-Exterior & -Interior) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stephen Bury (Front & Back) - New York, USA (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Amy Pragnell (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - L Carpenter - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Antoni Miro (Envelope-Front, ‘Reinventar-se 2014,’ & Inserts) - Spain (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Katherine Dolgy Ludwig (Front, Back, & Inside) - Canada (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Stefan Engstrom (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Natasha De Samarkandi (Inserts) - England (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Carol Neal (Packaging, ‘Rear View’ Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - George Oeser (Envelope-Back & Insert) - The Netherlands (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - R W Tannler (Copies of Original Mail Art from the 1940’s) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Florian Seebauer, Germany (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Pagiel Griffith - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cascadia Artpost (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Washington, USA (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Jim Sherraden (Front & Back, Insert-Front & -Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Stacy Irvin ‘MARFA TEXAS ‘MERICA’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Judith Hill - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Greg Nehrbass (Open View) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Penny Webb (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Mona Lisa Warren (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dane Carder (Envelope-Front, -Back & Inserts) - Tennessee, USA (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Jason Brown ‘Reinvention-Peter Liversidge Mail Art 2000’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Marc Lacuesta ‘Winchester Uber Alles’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Dana Neal (Envelope-Front & -Back, Insert-Front & -Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Dwayne Breeding - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - S M Leary (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - M Kimbrell ‘Klimt Geishas’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jackie Osborne (Box-Front & -Back, Contents-Front & -Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Beth Inglish ‘Release’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ed Barlow ‘Think for yourself’ - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Robbie Hunsinger (Insert) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Hari Babu Krishnan, India (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sara Lee Burd ‘Best Wishes’ - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Emily Naff ‘Post Office, Drapers, Jamaica’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Celene Aubry (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Kelly Copas (Front & Back) - Kentucky, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Rhendi Greenwell - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ed Barlow (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Jake Wells - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Brian Granger ‘Storytelling’ (Open View) - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - John Yandall - Tennessee, USA (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tulio Restrepo (Front & Back) - Colombia (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Kevin Anthuis (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Heidi Schwartz (Letter, Paint Dress, Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Caravan Gallery (Envelope-Front & -Back) & ‘The Man with the Green Man Tattoo’ - England (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Greece (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Michele Barone (Box-Top, -Underside, & Open View) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Jerry Winnett - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Belinda Smith (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Otto D Sherman (Front & Back) - New York, USA - missing (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - David Morel ‘One of Nine’ (Front & Back) - Sent from Juan Jose Murillo, Chile (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Tulio Restrepo (Front & Back) - Colombia (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - JHE - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shawn Jackson (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Connie Garrett ‘Reinvention’ - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Lenka Clayton & Michael Crowe - England (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Platetone (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Enzo Salanitro - Italy (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lothar Trott (Front & Back) - Switzerland (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Michael Paul (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Virginia, USA (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lillian Carland Malbasic (Envelope-Front) & ‘Reinvented Design’ - Serbia (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Continuing Mail from Duncan MacAskill (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Publications - Nashville Arts Magazine - April & August 2014 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Publications - Nashville Scene - August 21-27, 2014 - oversize (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Publications - Number: Seventy Seven - Winter 2014 - oversize (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Publications - The Tennessean Portfolio - Sunday, August 17, 2014 - oversize (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ephemera - Hatch Show Print: Nashville Calling (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention Wall Mount - East Side Story (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention Wall Mount - Howlin’ Books (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention Wall Mount - Mickey’s Tavern (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention Wall Mount - Nashville Arts Magazine (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Seth McInteer (Front, Back, & Insert - Broken) - Tennessee, USA (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Igor Jovanovie (Insert) - Serbia (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Donald Smith ‘Colour Space 2014’ (Front & Back) - England (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Elisa Battistella (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Italy (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ned Luberecki (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Ed Barlow (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Jim Sherraden (Front & Back, Insert-Front & -Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kelly Copas (Front & Back) - Kentucky, USA (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rhendi Greenwell - Tennessee, USA (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ed Barlow (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Kevin Anthuis (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kelley Luberecki ‘At the Feeder’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Publications - Nashville Scene - August 21-27, 2014 - oversize (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Publications - Number: Seventy Seven - Winter 2014 - oversize (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Publications - The Tennessean Portfolio - Sunday, August 17, 2014 - oversize (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera - Reinvention Mail Art Show Poster (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera - “Thank You” from the Curator (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ephemera - Hatch Show Print: Nashville Calling Poster (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jennifer A. Weigel - Missouri, USA (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Shauna Richardson (Top View & Under View) - England (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Jon Smith ‘POP GUN’ (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Susan Forsyth (Package & Sculpture ‘Mignon 2014’) - England (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Kelly Kessler ‘Felix Baumgartner & Geoffrey Chaucer hang out in an Akkadian medium’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - L Carpenter - Tennessee, USA (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Carol Neal (Packaging, ‘Rear View’ Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sara Lee Burd ‘Best Wishes’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ed Barlow ‘Think for yourself’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Michele Barone (Box-Top, -Underside, & Open View) - Tennessee, USA (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Connie Garrett ‘Reinvention’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Marc Lacuesta ‘Winchester Uber Alles’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - the kite (Box 18, Folder 1)
- “Letter to Me” Mail Art Project # 2
  - Unknown – USA (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Horst Tress – Germany (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jude Weirmeir – USA (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Daniele Virgilio – Italy (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cernjul Viviana – Argentina (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jaromir Svozilik – Norway (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Vittore Baroni – Italy (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Simon – England (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Lex Loeb – USA (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Tulio Peraza – Spain (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chuck Beard – USA (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Jose Roberto Sechi – Brazil (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Stacey Irvin – New Zealand (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Andre Pace – USA (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ryosuke Cohen – Japan (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lutz Beeke – Germany (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Wheeling Ice – USA (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Eni Elis – Brazil (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Emma Klee – USA (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Alevtina Nikonova – Russia (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cheryl Penn – South Africa (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dorian Ribas Marinho – Brazil (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - John Jennings – Ireland (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Moan Lisa – USA (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Michel Della Vedona – France (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Joel ‘Sticker Dude’ Cohen – USA (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Peter Kaufmann’PWK’ – Switzerland (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Daniel de Culla – Spain (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Otto D. Sherman – USA (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Valentine mark Herman – France (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Michael Goetz – USA (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Piet Franzen/SIDAC – The Netherlands (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Carlyle Baker – Canada (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Norbert Koczorski – Germany (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Monica Rex – USA (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Matthew Rose – France (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Katerina Kikoltsou – Greece (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Sassu Antonio – Italy (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Robert Ridley-Shackleton – England (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Susie Hamilton – England (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - John M. Bennett – USA (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Diane Kelp – USA (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Emilio Marandi – Italy (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Natasha De Samarkandi – England (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Miguel Jimenez – Spain (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Jim Leftwich – USA (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Michael Goetz – USA (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Students at Trakya University, Edirne, Turkey – Part 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Students at Trakya University, Edirne, Turkey – Part 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ken Miller – USA (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bruno Chairlone – Italy (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - John Held, Jr. – USA (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - EVER ARTS – The Netherlands (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rosanna Veronesi – Italy (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Judy Boyd – USA (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Moan Lisa – USA (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bernard Zilling – Germany (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence Weiner – USA (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Keith Bates – England (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Johan Van Geluwe – Belgium (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Jurgen O. Olbrich – Germany (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Enzo Salanitro – Italy (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Giovanni and Renata StraDA DA (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Unknown – USA (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Antonio Miro – Spain (Box 19, Folder 10b)
  - GX Jupitter-Larsen – USA (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mark Pawson – England (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lancillotto Bellini – Italy (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Pietro Romano Matarrese – Italy (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mars Tokyo – USA (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reed Altemus – USA (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Gandha Key – England (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Alexander Limarev – Russia (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Snappy – Canada (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Silvano Pertone – Italy (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Keiichi Nakamura – Japan (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Shauna Richardson – England (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Linda Pelati – Italy (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Battistella Elisa – Italy (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ryosuke Cohen – Japan (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Borderline Grafix – USA (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Anna Banana – Canada (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Torma Cauli – Hungary (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Wendy “Sky Queen” Whittemore – USA (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Carol Stetser – USA (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Jaromir Svozilik – Norway (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Judy Skolnick – USA (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Kurt Beaulieu – Canada (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Roberto Scala – Italy (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Katherine Dolgy Ludwig – Canada (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reid Wood – USA (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Colin Scholl – USA (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Dione Rabelo – Brazil (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ko De Jonge – The Netherlands (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Edna Toffoli – Brazil (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Peter Kaufmann PWK – Switzerland (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sofia Ludwig – Canada (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cuan Miles – South Africa (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jay Skiles – USA (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Marie-Christine de Grave – Belgium (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rod Summers/VEC – The Netherlands (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mars Tokyo – USA (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Cheryl Penn – South Africa (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Paul Tiilila – Finland (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jose Roberto Sechi – Brazil (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Henning Mittendorf – Germany (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Miche-Art-Universalis – Belgium (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Anne L. Braunschweig – USA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Tiziana Baracchi – Italy (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Private World – USA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Jennifer – USA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Anja Mattila-Tolvanen – Finland (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Collab Festival – USA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - BamBam Art – England (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Connie Jean – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sonata Stanton – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Duncan Ragsdale – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sheila Wright – Canada (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rachel Heinold – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Colin Scholl – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Tim Torkildson – USA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jeff Bertrand – USA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Pamela Butler – USA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Chris James – Australia (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sonia Albuquerque – Brazil (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Kelly Kessler – USA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Walter Pennacchi – Italy (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Caroline Saville – USA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fabiana Pereira – Argentina (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Juliana Hellmundt – Germany (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - John Butler – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kelley Luberecki – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - SIMONSON – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Ned Luberecki – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - C Thomas – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Victor Femenias Von Willigmann – Chile (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mark Sonnenfeld – USA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Students at the Warren Regional Juvenile Detention Center in Bowling Green, KY USA (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Judith Hill – USA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kelly Copas – USA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Igor Jovanovic – Serbia (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hanna Bayer – Germany (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Andrea Jay – USA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Serse Luigetti – Italy (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Laura Moody – USA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kelly Copas – USA (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Mara Pauline – USA (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Wendy Whittemore – USA (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Aaron Smith – USA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Juanita Tumelaire – USA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mandy Argue – USA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Belinda Smith –USA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Chad M. Kelsey – USA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Kaaren Hirschowitz Engel – USA (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ray Richardson – England (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Gabriele Astrid Hoppe – Germany (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Andrea Jenkins – USA (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Celene Aubry – Italy (4 cards) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Jim Sherraden – USA (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Susan Forsyth – England (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Oznur Kepce – Turkey (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Anna Karina Fries – Germany (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Richard – USA (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Jose Luis Alcalde Soberanes – Mexico (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dame Mailarta – Canada (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Printed invitations to participate in “Letter to Me” mail art project (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Flashdrive containing mail art images and database (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ed Barlow – USA (Box 22, Folder 1)